dolphinmusic.co.uk 2019-12-25

# Privacy Policy PMT Online

**PMT Online Privacy Policy**

S & T Audio Ltd (“PMT Online”) respects your privacy and provides this Privacy Policy to identify the types of information we collect, how it is used, your rights with respect to that data, and how you may contact us regarding your data.

PMT Online may modify this policy at any time either by providing your email notification and/or via a notification on our home page. For your information, this policy was last updated on May 23rd, 2018.

**Information We Collect and How We Use It**

When using our web site, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, phone number or other details to help you with your experience.

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the web site, or use certain other web site features in the following ways:

• To personalise your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.  
• To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.  
• To send periodic emails regarding your basket, your order or other products and services.

When you open an account or sign up for email communications to our web site, you will receive an email from us asking you to confirm your email address - this gives us confirmation that you want to receive emails from us.

If you add a product to your basket on our web site, we may send you an abandoned basket email. By adding a product to your basket shows intent to purchase and allows us to send you this email.

**Retail Stores**

Currently, we have multiple retail stores across the UK. When you make a purchase from one of our stores you’ll be asked if you want to join our mailing list. Your order data and contact details are stored in our centralised database. This same database contains all of our customer information irrespective of where our customers have purchased from. The same security is given to your data regardless of where you’ve purchased from.

**Information Collected by Automated Means**

Information is collected through cookies, log files, link tracking, and/or third parties. Some of the collected information is tied to your personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the web site for you.

**Cookies**

 ****Cookies are small files that a web site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the web site systems to recognise your web browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us maintain sessions when logged into the PMT Online web site. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current web site activity. This enables us to provide you with an improved service. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about web site traffic and web site interaction so that we can offer better web site experiences and tools in the future.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your web browser (such as IE, Chrome, Safari or Firefox) settings. Each web browser is a little different, so look at your web browser’s “Help” menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you disable cookies, some features will be disabled. It is not recommended to disable cookies as it will impact your ability to use the PMT Online web site.

**Log Files**

Web site log files are used to store information such as: internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks. This information is used to analyse trends, administer the web site, track your movement within the web site and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

**Information Retention**

 ****PMT Online will retain personal information, customer and business information for as long as it is needed to provide services and/or products that you have requested; to communicate with you about a request you have made; to comply with our legal and regulatory obligations, to demonstrate compliance, and to enforce PMT Online rights and agreements.

**How We Share Your Personal Information**

 ****PMT Online may share your information with companies that provide services to help us with our business activities (and who are obligated to maintain the confidentiality of the information); in response to lawful requests from public authorities; with a related business entity in connection with a merger or corporate reorganisation or as may be necessary to comply with the law, enforce our web site policies or protect third parties’ or PMT Online rights, property and safety.  
**  
Data Security**

 ****Safeguarding the information that you give us or we receive about you is a priority for PMT Online. We take appropriate security measures to protect against loss, misuse and unauthorised access, alteration, disclosure, or destruction of your information and have security awareness and training for the relevant members of our staff, including management.

**Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information**

 ****If you would like to view, update, or remove the personal information we have relating to you, please email us your request at mydata@pmtonline.co.uk

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at unsubscribe@pmtonline.co.uk and our systems will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.

**Contact Information**

 ****If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

**PMT Online**  
48-50 Queens Road  
Southend On Sea  
SS1 1NL.

Email: [mydata@pmtonline.co.uk](mailto:mydata@pmtonline.co.uk)  
Telephone: 0151 448 2089

This privacy policy relates solely to this web site and our retail stores.
